http://www.americanvending.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

All Categories
ManufacturersEquipment by Manufacturer365 Retail MarketsAdrenaline Amusements All State MFGAmerican ChangerAmerican PinballAMSAndamiroApple IndustriesArachnid 360AzkoyenBandai-NamcoBarron GamesBay Tek EntertainmentBenchmarkBob's Space RacersChampionChicago GamingCoastal AmusementsCoast to CoastConluxCPICRANECrystal MountainDiamondElaut USAFood ConceptsFrameworks DisplaysGlobal VRGrindmasterICEIGTImberaIncredible TechnologiesJennison EntertainmentKalkomatLAI GamesMagic PlayMaxx SeatingMEIMicro Market FixturesN&WNautilusNectaNewcoNordonPanasonicParlevelRaw ThrillsRoyal VendorsSeagaSega AmusementsSharpSmart Industries Stern PinballTeam PlayThe Really Big Crane CompanyTornadoTouch Magix TouchtunesTriotechTritonUNISUSA TechnologiesUSIVendoValley-DynamoYokeUnit-EVirtuixGold Standard GamesOptConnectHabcoVRArsenalParts by ManufacturerAdrenaline PartsAMS PartsAndamiro PartsApple Industries PartsAP CoffeeArachnid PartsBandai-Namco PartsBarron Games PartsBay Tek Entertainment PartsBenchmark PartsBob's Space Racers PartsCoastal Amusement PartsCoast to Coast PartsCrane PartsDelta ForemostElaut USA PartsFood Concepts PartsICE PartsIGT PartsImbera PartsIncredible Technologies PartsJennison Entertainment PartsKalkomat PartsLAI Games PartsRaw Thrills PartsRoyal Vendors PartsRTC PartsSega Amusements PartsStern PartsSUZOHAPP PartsTouchPoint ScienceUNIS PartsUSA Technologies PartsUSI PartsValley-Dynamo PartsVendent PartsVendo PartsParts / AccessoriesAmusement PartsManufacturersAndamiroArachnidBay Tek EntertainmentBenchmarkBromleyCardtronicsHAPPICERaw ThrillsStern PinballTouchPoint ScienceCategoriesCovid-19Pool & DartsGaming PartsManufacturersAVSIGTSpieloTouchPoint ScienceCategories CabinetElectronicsHardwarePeripheralsPreventative Maintenance PartsSignageAir FiltersAudio ComponentsBack Plates, Backplanes, Game BoardsBallastsBatteriesBezelsButtonsCard ReadersCPUsCovid-19DisplaysGraphics CardsHarnessesKeypadsLabelsLamp HoldersLED Display BoardsLED PanelsPower SuppliesSwitchesTouch ScreensVideo CardsVending PartsManufacturersAP CoffeeCraneDixieImberaNorthern Lights LEDPremium Product GroupRTCTouchPoint ScienceUSIVendoVendentCategoriesAdaptors & NozzlesArmaturesBezelBrackets, Latches & PlatesBrew ChambersBrew CylindersBucketsCamsCanisters, Lids, Dividers & CoversCarriagesChutesCleaning SuppliesCoffee Grinders & ImpellersCoin Cups, Ramps & ChutesControl BoardsCooler Baskets, Trays, SlidesCovid-19Delivery Doors, Cupwell Doors, Gates, FramesDelivery PortsDiaphrams, BootsDisplaysEvaporator CoilsFansFilters, HousingsFloatsGasket, SealsGrillGrommetsHarness, Cables, Line CordsHeating ElementsKitsLED LightsLight Bulbs, Fuses, Bulb SocketsLocksMixing BowlsMotorsPistonsPrice Labels, DecalsShims, SpacersSpirals, Helix Adaptors, Product PushersSpringsSwitchesTemperature Probes, Timers, Relays, Thermostats, Cold ControlsT-HandlesToolsTransformersTrimTubingValves, Brew, CommodityWheels, CommodityEquipmentGaming EquipmentVideo Gaming TerminalsGame TitlesManufacturersPayout SystemsManufacturersIGTSpieloM3TAEPMLPMaxx SeatingAccessoriesSeating EquipmentMachine BasesManufacturersAmusement EquipmentBar / Sports EquipmentManufacturersDartsTable HockeyFoosballShuffleboardShooting GalleryBasketball GamesBoxingPool TablesTest of StrengthArcade EquipmentManufacturersShooting GalleryRacing GamesRhythm GamesShoot 'em UpSportsArcade GamesCompetitionPhoto Booths EquipmentManufacturersMisc Amusement EquipmentManufacturersTicket Dispenser Prize RedemptionTicket CounterTicket Redemption EquipmentManufacturersSportsPusherWheelTossArcade GamesSkillCraneDropButton PresserShooterKiddie RIdeWater GamesSpinnerWhackerPrize Merchandisers EquipmentManufacturersCranePrize DispenserPinball MachinesManufacturersKiddie RidesManufacturersCarouselTrainDrivingFEC AttractionsManufacturersManufacturersAdrenaline AmusementsAmerican PinballAndamiroApple IndustriesArachnid 360Bandai-NamcoBarron GamesBay Tek EntertainmentBenchmark GamesBob's Space RacersChampionChicago GamingCoastal AmusementsCoast to Coast EntertainmentCreative WorksDiamond Elaut USAGlobal VRGold Standard GamesICE Incredible TechnologiesJennison EntertainmentKalkomatLAI GamesMagic PlayParisiRaw ThrillsRocket AmusementsSega AmusementsSMART IndustriesStern PinballTeam PlayThe Really Big Crane CompanyTouch MagixTriotechUNISUnit-EValley-DynamoVirtuixVRArsenalVending EquipmentCoffee Vendor EquipmentCoffee Vendor EquipmentOffice Coffee SystemsManufacturersBeverage Vendor EquipmentManufacturersSnack Vendor EquipmentManufacturersSnack / Beverage Combo EquipmentManufacturersMisc. Vending EquipmentManufacturersCold Food EquipmentRefrigerated EquipmentFrozen EquipmentManufacturersMicro MarketsManufacturersCoolersManufacturersManufacturersAMSCraneRoyal VendorsMicro Market FixturesUSIFood ConceptsVendoNorthern Lights LEDUSA TechnologiesCrystal MountainSeagaNectaAll State MFGAzkoyenGrindmasterImberaPanasonicPremium Product GroupN&WFrameworks DisplaysNordonParlevel365 Retail MarketsNewcoSharpYokeHabcoCoin & Currency EquipmentPayment SystemsManufacturersBill ChangersManufacturersManufacturers MeiAmerican ChangerConluxCPIUSA Technologies OptConnectJukeboxesAMI Entertainment EquipmentTouchTunesManufacturersAMITouchtunesHome ProductsManufacturersBandai-NamcoBarron GamesBob's Space RacersChampionIncredible TechnologiesSheltiStern PinballTornadoValley-DynamoBay Tek EntertainmentFoosballShuffleboardPool TablesATMsManufacturersTritonNautilusAbout UsTestimonialsAchievementsSupportFinancing / Repair / RefurbishingDownloadsAVS NewsEventsContactBlog
More Categories
Home
Contact
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
American Vending Sales Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which American Vending Sales collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.americanvending.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by American Vending Sales.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, fill out a form, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
American Vending Sales may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our Site
We may need your information to display content on the Site correctly.
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To process payments
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Electronic newsletters
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Advertising
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Compliance with children's online privacy protection act
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Changes to this privacy policy
American Vending Sales has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
This document was last updated on June 7, 2016
